debshops.com 2016-04-03

# Trendy Plus Size Clothing for Women | Deb Shops

Softree Inc. (“Debshops”) values our customers and respects your privacy. We collect information about you in our stores and through our Website in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests, and promotions. As described in this policy, we may share your information among our brands, as may be applicable, and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service. We may also share your information when we are legally required to do so.

This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use and protect it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. By providing your personal information to Debshops, you are consenting to the manner in which we collect, use, disclose, protect, and otherwise manage that information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated version of the policy on our Website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears above the date on which the new policy becomes effective. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our website and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. Your continued use of our Website constitutes your consent to be bound by the revised policy. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us via mail or phone.  

### What kind of information does Debshops collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit our Website, store, place an order online or by phone, make a purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone and in our stores. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners and from unrelated third parties.  

### How does Debshops use my information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:  
  • To process and fulfill your order, including sending you emails to confirm your order status and shipment   
  • To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications   
  • To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions   
  • To help us learn more about your shopping preferences   
  • To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services   
  • To enhance your shopping experience in our stores or online   
  • To analyze trends and statistical data  
  • To protect the security or integrity of our Website and our business   
  • To contact you if necessary 

You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls. For instructions on opting out, please see the section below entitled, "How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?"

### Does Debshops share my information?

We may share your personal information in the following ways:  
  • We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.   
  • We may share your information when we team up with another company to offer or provide products, services, contests, or promotions to our customers.   
  • We may share your information if necessary to comply with laws or regulations or in response to a valid subpoena, order, or government request, or to protect the rights of Debshops. 

In addition, if you choose to participate in any third-party scrip, loyalty, or similar program in which a Debshops brand is a participating vendor, and you authorize Debshops or our credit card processor to provide information about your purchases to the company administering the program, we will share your personal information with that program. In the unlikely event of a sale or merger of Debshops or any of our businesses, assets or brands, our customers' personal information and other information we have collected as described in this policy may be among the transferred business assets.  

### How do I access or change my information?

You can review and change certain personal information related to your use of our online sites, such as your name and contact information. To access your information at a Debshops Website, simply sign in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your personal information in your account profile.

You can also request us to update your personal information by contacting us as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?" Please note that any request to update your personal information may take up to ten business days for your email request and six to eight weeks for your postal mail request.  

### How do I make choices about receiving promotional communications?

On March 10, 2015, certain personally identifiable information of the customers of Deb Stores Holding LLC and its affiliates were sold and transferred to Debshops. Debshops wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, from one or more of our brands, you can let us know by contacting our customer service as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?".

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase from the Debshops brand. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to ten business days to process your email request and six to eight weeks to process your postal mail request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from Debshops. If you change your mind, you can start receiving promotional communications from us again by logging into your online account and changing your preferences, by signing up when you visit our Website or our stores, or when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, or by contacting customer service. Please note that when you make an online purchase from us, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order.

### How does Debshops protect kids' privacy?

Debshops is concerned about the privacy and safety of children when they use the Internet. We will never knowingly request or collect personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of thirteen without prior verifiable parental consent. Our Website is a general audience site and is not targeted to or intended for use by children.  

### How does Debshops use cookies?

Our Website use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a Website. Cookies enable you to shop on our Website and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience.

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain Website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our Website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our Website. Cookies may also be used to collect transaction information needed by a scrip or loyalty program to which you have authorized us to provide your personal information. (See the section above entitled, "Does Debshops share my information?")

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you set your browser to not accept cookies, then please contact our customer service as described in the section below entitled, "How do I contact you?".  

### How does Debshops use pixel tags?

We use "pixel tags" (also called "web beacons" or "clear gifs"), which are tiny graphic images, on our Website and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our Website and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the Website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other Websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We also work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our Website and your interaction with our advertising and other communications. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having your information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our Website, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.  

### How do I know my personal information is secure?

We take precautions, including the use of encryption technologies and authentication tools, to protect the security of your personal information and to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our Website, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock, depending upon your browser, then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https."  

### What is "phishing"?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information, or other personal information through email.  

### What about links to other Websites?

For your convenience and information, our Website may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.  

### How do I contact you?

For questions about our privacy policy, to make choices about receiving promotional communications, or to update your personal information, you can contact Debshops by email, telephone, or postal mail:

Debshops Customer Service  
3232 E Washington Blvd  
Vernon, CA 90058  
support@debshops.com  
1-888-926-3045  

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Debshops who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the above address with the attention to Debshops (California Privacy Rights).

When you visit the Debshops Website, we collect customer information to improve the content of our Website for marketing and promotional purposes. Each time you visit our Website, our Web server automatically recognizes your IP address, monitor resolution and what type of browser you are using. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, and collect customer information gathered in the course of joining our online member base and/or processing sales transactions. We do not gather any personally identifying information about you when you visit this Website, unless you choose to provide such information to us. If you supply us with your email address, you may receive periodic emails from us announcing product information, promotional events, or updates to our Website. If you do not wish to receive such email updates please contact us to opt out as described in the section above entitled, "How do I contact you?"

We may use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.   

### Children

We do not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children (minors younger than thirteen years old). If you are a parent and believe we may have inadvertently collected such information from your child, please contact us immediately as described in the section above entitled, "How do I contact you?"  

### Cookies

When you view our Website, we may store some information on your computer's hard drive. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie." Cookies enable us to establish the shopping cart session and allow you to purchase items on-line at our Website. Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but you can change your browser setting to not accept Cookies. Without accepting a Cookie, you can browse through our Website, but you will be unable to establish a shopping cart session and make a purchase online.  

### Security

This Website makes every effort to protect your online order information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL encrypts your order information to ensure it remains private and secure. To check the security of your connection, check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the Website will change from "http" to "https". You may also see a closed lock or unbroken key image. This also indicates that your session on our website is secure using SSL.

Some browsers and firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers. In that case, you will be unable to connect to our server so you will not have to worry about mistakenly placing an order through an unsecured connection.

* * *
